Finding Aid for Holy Cross Church (Cross Village, Mich.) records, 1847-1930
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Holy Cross Church (Cross Village, Mich.) records 1847-1930
Holy Cross Church (Cross Village, Mich.).
1 microfilm reel
86934 Ba Microcopy
Baptismal records, marriage, birth and death records, photographs, newspaper clippings and printed histories detailing activities of this Indian church.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The records were made available for microfilming by the church (donor no. 5337 ).
No further additions to the records are expected.
The record group is open to research.
The original records are held by the church.
Holy Cross Church is a Catholic church which ministered to the Native American community of Cross Village, Michigan.
The records of the church date back to 1847 and include baptismal records, marriage, birth and death records, photographs, newspaper clippings and printed histories detailing activities of this Indian church. Most of the records are in Latin and Ottawa.
Subjects:
Cross Village (Mich.); Catholic Church--Missions--Michigan--Cross Village.; Catholic Church--Michigan--Cross Village.; Holy Cross Church (Cross Village, Mich.); Indians of North America--Missions--Michigan--Cross Village.; Indians of North America--Michigan--Cross Village.; Emmet County (Mich.); Registers of births, etc.--Michigan--Cross Village.
- Church records
  - Historical notes (Reel 1)
  - Baptismal records, 1847-1868 (Reel 1)
    (in Latin and Ottawa)
  - Marriage, birth and death records, 1847-1868 (Reel 1)
    (In Latin and Ottawa)
  - Death records, 1847-1868 (Reel 1)
  - Church records, 1867-1870 (Reel 1)
    (in Latin)
  - Church records, ca. 1868-1895 (Reel 1)
  - Church records, 1901-1908 (Reel 1)
  - Church records, 1908-1920 (Reel 1)
    (In English and Ottawa)
  - Church records, 1921-1930 (Reel 1)
    (In English and Polish)
  - Miscellaneous church records (Reel 1)
  - Photographs (Reel 1)
  - Newspaper clippings and printed histories (Reel 1)